Now I have to ask you this question and
现在我向你提出一个问题
likely many of our students are pondering it as well.
这也是我们许多学员在思考的问题
So, will AI replace all our jobs?
人工智能是否取代我们所有的工作？
Will it take over the world?
它是否会统治世界？
How worried should we be?
我们该有多担心呀？
I was waiting for that priceless question.
我之前就预想到这个非常有趣的问题
First and foremost, our leader, Ginni Rometty,
首先我们的领袖 Ginni Rometty
has coined the term Augmented Intelligence, not artificial intelligence.
创造了增强智能(Augmented Intelligence) 这个术语 不是人工智能
Our capabilities are here not to supplant jobs but to help
我们这里的能力 (Capabilities) 不是取代工作
remove the mundane tasks so workers can focus on the core mission.
而是帮助取消单调的任务 这样工人们可以专注于核心任务
Yes, they will require new training and we call that
对 他们需要新的培训 我们可以说这是
new collar jobs and that is exactly what our partnership with Udacity is providing.
新领工作 这也是优达学城提供的合作关系
So yes, we are rapidly approaching an inflection point in
对 我们快速进入人类历史的拐点
human history where Augmented Intelligence will
增强智能会
exceed human intelligence and debates about humans
超越人类智慧 引发公众对于人机交互
versus machines have become part of our common vernacular.
的讨论与热议
How can we prepare our next generation of students to compete?
我们怎么让下一代学员做好准备竞争呢？
One positive step being taken in our K
我们在 K 到 12 年级采取的积极步骤
through 12 schools is a growing emphasis on STEM: science technology,
是更加重视 STEM 课程 即科学 技术
engineering and mathematics education,
工程和数学的教育
plus modern coding skills.
以及现代编码技能
For example, IBM's P-TECH program,
例如 IBM 的 P-TECH 课程
where students graduate with a high school diploma and
其中计算机或工程专业高中文凭毕业生和
an associate degree in computers or engineering.
大专文凭毕业生
But STEM education is not enough,
不过 STEM 教育并不够
and that is where our partnership comes in.
所以这是我们合作关系出现的原因
Jeffrey Calvin in his book,
杰夫·科尔文 (Geoff Colvin) 在书中
"Humans Are Underrated: What High Achievers Know That Brilliant Machines
《不会被机器替代的人：智能时代的生存策略》 (Humans Are Underrated: What High Achievers Know That Brilliant Machines Never Will)
Never Will," argues that it is right brain skills like creativity,
指出正确的大脑技能 例如创造力
imagination, collaboration, holistic thinking,
想象力 协作能力 整体思维
and emotional intelligence that are the greatest source of
和情商是人类对抗机器的
competitive advantage for humans versus machines.
竞争性优势的最大来源
Thank you so much for giving us such a comprehensive tour of
非常感谢你带领我们完成了
natural language processing and artificial intelligence.
自然语言处理和人工智能的综合性旅程
Absolutely, our mission at IBM Watson is to bring
没错 我们在 IBM Watson 的使命是
the cutting edge cognitive technologies within reach of everyone.
把前沿认知技能带给每个人
There's no reason for Augmented Intelligence to stay locked
增强智能不能只停留在研究室中
up in research labs and in the hands of a few companies.
也不能掌握在少数公司中
With the power of IBM Watson behind you I
在 IBM Watson 的努力下
can't even imagine what applications you'll end up building.
我现在还无法想象你最后构建出的应用程序
Let's get started today.
我们现在开始吧